Yaeli sheinberger

🔀 yaeli8454@gmail.com 🤳 0548410992

Education

Computer Science (B.Sc) 2020 - 2024

Bachelor's student at the Open University.

Specializes in business management and 2016 - 2020

accounting.

High School, Ministry of Education.

2023 - 2023 Full Stack Web Development

HackerU Campus

Employment

Course guidance for learning Python

Apr 2023 - Present Guiding high school students the language studies from 0 prior knowledge, to mastering the language and submitting a final project.

In the PyCharm workspace.

Secretary at Mayanot College

2022 - 2023 Temporary work at the same time as studies,

Management in the college offices, registrations, information, collection of funds.

Extracurricular activities

Drachi Miriam Association at Shaare Zedek

Hospital

Supporting the sick families by showing interest and distributing food.

Ezer mizion

Caring for children with special needs.

2022 - 2023

Mentor for elementary school girls who have difficulty in studies.

projects and achievements

Salas mentoring project for students

Chosen based on academic excellence to guide female students in the first and second year of the courses:

* Introduction to computer science and the Java language A. * Differential and integral calculus B.

The hackathon project

Website development for a babysitter matching service. Made in Java language, including design, PoC development.

Personal details

LinkedIn

linkedin.com/in/yaelisheinberger

profile

Fourth-year computer science student, with excellent interpersonal skills, high capacity for self-learning, experience in working under pressure, high responsibility and work ethic, serious, striving for excellence, motivated to learn and know more, passionate about researching and solving problems.

skills

Java, c, Python, SQL, JavaScript, css, HTML5

Languages

Hebrew

2021 - 2023

Native language English High level